{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of mobile device operating systems.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which OS is made by Google?",
      "answers": ["Android", "iOS", "Harmony"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS is used in iPhones?",
      "answers": ["iOS", "Android", "Windows"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS is known for its tiles interface?",
      "answers": ["Windows", "iOS", "Android"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS is developed by Huawei?",
      "answers": ["Harmony", "iOS", "Android"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS was used in Blackberry phones?",
      "answers": ["BB OS", "Symbian", "Android"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS is open-source?",
      "answers": ["Android", "iOS", "Windows"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS is known for its security?",
      "answers": ["iOS", "Android", "Symbian"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS uses the App Store?",
      "answers": ["iOS", "Android", "Harmony"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS is made by Samsung?",
      "answers": ["Tizen", "iOS", "Android"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which OS was developed by Nokia?",
      "answers": ["Symbian", "iOS", "Windows"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
